http://www.autoseats.com/company/privacy-policy.php

AUTO SEATS PRIVACY POLICY
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, will only be used  to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
We do use cookies. Similar to other Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" and Web server logs sessions to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server session logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site.
What Are Cookies?
Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Children Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.autoseats.com/auto_seats_terms.php. By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes. If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
Auto Interior.1116 N. State Road 7Hollywood, FL 33021
OUR COMPANY
About Us
Cart & Checkout
FAQ & Help
Contact Us
Client's Reviews
Privacy Policy
Return Policy
Terms Of Use
Sitemap
Auto Interiors
1116 N State RD 7 Hollywood FL 33021 1.954.963.4989 1.954.558.2222 autoseat@autoseats.com
PRODUCTS & SERVICES
Allweather Floor Mats
Carpet Floor Mats
Camo Floor Mats
Dash Covers
Canvas Denim
Camouflage
Waterproof
WHAT OUR CLIENTS ARE SAYING
I received my seat covers the other day and I am very pleased, thank you very much! Kevin Harris
I just recieved the Gator seat covers. They look great. I would like to thank Jean Seat INC for there great customer service and great products! Thanks again Lt Phillip O'Connell
©2010 - 2020 Jean Seat International, INC.
